{
    "subject": "resource/Quinn_Cummings",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Los_Angeles",
    "human_readable": "Quinn Cummings was born in Los Angeles.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9319255948066711,
            "question": "Where was Quinn Cummings born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8372863531112671,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Quinn Cummings was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.544696033000946,
            "question": "What is Quinn Cummings known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3943064510822296,
            "question": "In what year did Quinn Cummings begin her acting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3844905495643616,
            "question": "At what age did Quinn Cummings first appear in a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37936532497406006,
            "question": "Besides acting, what other pursuits has Quinn Cummings been involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3112245798110962,
            "question": "Is Quinn Cummings still active in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25147923827171326,
            "question": "Which movie launched Quinn Cummings to fame?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24906882643699646,
            "question": "Did Quinn Cummings win any awards for her acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22021514177322388,
            "question": "What genre of films is Quinn Cummings known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Quinn Cummings was born in Los Angeles.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6623_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Quinn Cummings win any awards for her acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6623_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which movie launched Quinn Cummings to fame?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6623_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Quinn Cummings still active in the entertainment industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6623_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6623_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6623_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6623_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6623_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6623_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6623_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6623_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6623_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6623_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6623_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. Specifically, document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6623/re-ranker-msmarco/25.txt states that Quinn Cummings was born in Los Angeles, California."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Quinn Cummings, including her place of birth. All documents state that she was born in Los Angeles, California. Therefore, the statement \"Quinn Cummings was born in Los Angeles\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}